hello.





Armed with 8 years of on-hand agency experience, I am a well-rounded and versatile creative. As an insightful and strategic thinker, I believe in purpose-driven, relatable design and campaigns that deliver the work—the work that make our clients happy, the consumers excited, and our agency, proud.

Currently in: Arad, Romania

+40 772 019 602 hello@natassjavelasco.com

www.natassjavelasco.com

Education

2015 - 2016 Master in Advertising

Bournemouth University Bournemouth, United Kingdom

2010 - 2014 Bachelor in Advertising Arts

University of Santo Tomas

Manila, Philippines

Skills

IDEATION Storytelling, Insighting, 360

Campaign Conceptualization and Development, Strategy, Presentation, Social Media Content Creation, Brand

Identity Development

ART OOH & Print Design, Packaging
DIRECTION Design, Photography, Storyboarding,

Illustration, Character Design, Motion Graphics, Corporate Branding and Logo Design, Color Theory, Color Grading, Retouching, Storytelling,

UX/UI Design

SOFTWARE Proficiency with Adobe Creative

Suite- Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Knowledge of Motion Design, Animation and Editing with After Effects, Basic knowledge of Figma, Proficiency with Mac & Windows and office programs (Word,

Powerpoint and Keynote)

LANGUAGE English (Native, IELTS C1), German (B1),

Romanian (A1)

Industry Experience

FMCG Chips, Tea drinks, Wafers, Chocolates,

Ice creams, Soymilk, Instant Noodles

Healthcare Shampoo, Anti-Fungal topical treat-

ments, ED medicine, Pills

Services Low Cost Carriers, Cargo, Banks, Cable

and Internet providers

Experience

2017 - Present Senior Art Director at Seven A.D.

Responsibilities include conceptualization, supervision and implementation of various materials- from 360 and ATL campaigns, OOH, digital communications and pitches. I also act as a design lead for a few of our local brands, merging creative and management work, which includes overseeing production meetings, shoots and so much more.

During my time here, the agency has won 3 consecutive independent agency of the year, as well as a Seven Star award, given to employees who have exhibited exceptional work.

http://sevenad-ph.com/

2017 - 2019 Creative Director, Co-Founder at Parea

Branding Studio

Joint creative team focused on helping local businesses develop their visual identity.

www.instagram.com/parea.branding/

2014 - 2015 **Digital Creative** at Publicis Manila

Responsibilities include creating social media content for international brands such as Pantene, Vidal Sassoon,

Nescafe.

Awards

2018

2020 Silver Anvil for PSBank Millennials TVC

Awarded for effective communications

2019 **Seven Star Award,** Seven A.D.

Awarded for exceptional work

Adobo Design Awards Asia for Gugma Weaves

Bronze for corporate branding design

let's collaborate!